<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Researches on 0xSlaxo Blog</title>
    <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Researches on 0xSlaxo Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sl4x0.github.io/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Obfuscating Attacks with Encoding</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/obfuscating-attacks-w-encoding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/obfuscating-attacks-w-encoding/</guid>
      <description>This is my Notes about Obfuscation from PortSwigger
Context-specific decoding Client and Server side use decoding to pass data to systems decoding depends on context which data appears a query param = server side decode text content eg. html = client side decode When constructed attack = be carefull where the payload is being injected [Server Side - Client Side] Decoding discrepancies Injections involving on injecting payloads use reconginzalble patterns html tags javascript functions sql statements Website implement defenses to suspicious patterns Input Filters need to decode inputs to know if it is safe or not Its vital that the decoded perform when checking iputs is the same performed by backend Any discrepancy can enable an attacker to sneak harmful payloads past the filter by applying different encodings that will automatically be removed later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How i Use Notion with Bug Bounty and Pentesting Books</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/my-method-for-making-book-library-with-notion-for-bb-and-pentesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 15:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/my-method-for-making-book-library-with-notion-for-bb-and-pentesting/</guid>
      <description>You Can Duplicate the Template Form Here!
Introduction Hello Guys!👋 In This Article, I will Explain How I use Notion effectively for Taking Notes, Summarising and Reviewing Books for Bug Bounty, and other Pentesting Notes or Books.
So first of all we will use a notion’s function called “Table” or “Database” and It’s like what u imagine, Columns and Rows and within it, we can make a library.
So without further a do let’s start!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are web webservers?</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-web-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-web-servers/</guid>
      <description>What is the Internet First ? The internet is a **wire** a actually buried in the ground it might be fiber optics copper or occasionally beam to satellites or through cell phone networks but the internet is simply a wire.
The internet is useful because **two computers connected directly** to this wire can communicate a server is a special computer connected directly to the internet and **web pages** or **files** on that server&amp;rsquo;s **hard drive** every server has a unique **Internet Protocol** address or IP address just like a postal address IP addresses help computers find each other but since 72.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pentester, Types, Methodology and Career ?</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-pentester/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-pentester/</guid>
      <description>Pentesters assess the security of computers, networks, and websites by looking for and exploiting vulnerabilities–commonly known as hacking. &amp;ldquo;With great power comes great responsibility&amp;rdquo;.
Synonymous Terms and Types of Hackers White hat hackers: Ethical hackers (aka pentesters). Gray hat hackers: Gray hats fall into a fuzzy area. Their intent is not always malicious, but it is not always ethical either. Black hat hackers: Their intent and purpose are illegal. Cyber criminals fall into this category.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
