<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>basics on 0xSlaxo Blog</title>
    <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/tags/basics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in basics on 0xSlaxo Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:10:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sl4x0.github.io/tags/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Application Firewalls (WAFs) for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/books/waf-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/books/waf-for-dummies/</guid>
      <description>This is a summary of the book &amp;ldquo;Web Application Firewalls (WAFs)&amp;rdquo; from F5 Security.
Understanding WAF Basics In today’s digital economy, web applications are a primary target for attackers. Traditional security tools don’t provide adequate protection for your business-critical applications.
Looking at Essential WAF Capabilities A WAF protects applications by applying a set of rules to the Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) or Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure (HTTPS) sessions that web applications use for communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are web webservers?</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-web-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-web-servers/</guid>
      <description>What is the Internet First ? The internet is a **wire** a actually buried in the ground it might be fiber optics copper or occasionally beam to satellites or through cell phone networks but the internet is simply a wire.
The internet is useful because **two computers connected directly** to this wire can communicate a server is a special computer connected directly to the internet and **web pages** or **files** on that server&amp;rsquo;s **hard drive** every server has a unique **Internet Protocol** address or IP address just like a postal address IP addresses help computers find each other but since 72.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pentester, Types, Methodology and Career ?</title>
      <link>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-pentester/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sl4x0.github.io/research/what-is-pentester/</guid>
      <description>Pentesters assess the security of computers, networks, and websites by looking for and exploiting vulnerabilities–commonly known as hacking. &amp;ldquo;With great power comes great responsibility&amp;rdquo;.
Synonymous Terms and Types of Hackers White hat hackers: Ethical hackers (aka pentesters). Gray hat hackers: Gray hats fall into a fuzzy area. Their intent is not always malicious, but it is not always ethical either. Black hat hackers: Their intent and purpose are illegal. Cyber criminals fall into this category.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
